# **Lucio Franco**

I am Lucio Franco, currently a 19 year old Computer Science student at the University of Denver. I have a strong passion for learning, solving problems and programming. I have experience writing APIs, Games, and Web Apps. I am currently in the process of learning Go, RUST, and Haskell. I am very interested in distributed systems and functional programming.

2194 South High Street #274,
Denver, CO, 80210
(240)-688-6461
lucio.franco@du.edu
https://luciofran.co
https://github.com/LucioFran
co

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Ombud,** Denver, CO — Software Engineer Intern

https://ombud.com

MAR 2015 - PRESENT

Ombud helps companies sell products faster. I worked there as a Software Engineer intern working with Coffeescript/react, Node/express, and Elasitcsearch and Mysql.

## **X30,** Kensington, MD — IT Intern

http://x3o.com

AUG 2013 - JAN 2014

X30 was an IT consultant company based in Rockville, Maryland. I Built software to automatically download base software for new computers.

### **EDUCATION**

# **University of Denver,** Denver, CO — Honors B.S. in Computer Science

SEPT 2014 - JUNE 2018

Courses: Computer Organization, Intro to Algorithms, Discrete Structures

#### **PROJECTS**

## RobustEngine — Java OpenGL 2d Game Engine

Game Engine written with LWJGL with builtin state system, map system, and tile system. <a href="https://github.com/LucioFranco/RobustEngine">https://github.com/LucioFranco/RobustEngine</a>

https://github.com/LucioFranco/RobustExample

All of my projects are hosted on github!

#### **SKILLS**

Javascript, Java, Ruby, Go, C/C++, HTML/CSS/JS, Git, OSS

React, Angular, CoffeeScript, SASS, gulp, make

Docker, Nginx, DigitalOcean, MongoDB, Elasticsearch, PostgreSQL, Mysql, Nodejs

#### **AWARDS**

Walter Johnson High School Computer Science Award

2nd place at Startup Weekend DU

### **LANGUAGES**

English, French, Italian